it's time to play Amazon book fair job
fair
Edition the US Department of Labor says
unemployment is down and for the second
straight month job numbers are the best
they've been in seven years you hear
that at midnight viewers brush off those
Cheeto
crumbs or as I call it unemployment
dust and get a godamn job so manans in
honor the fact that Americans are back
to work we're going to show you a bunch
of vocational books about some of our
most time honored professions and for
250 points you have to give me a chapter
in that book all right here's the first
one top 10 mistakes Pastors
make
damn kids say the most seductive things
[Applause]
[Laughter]
points uh Alex B um chapter two yeah but
stuff counts okay
points Mr PRS chapter seven why it's
wrong to ask a young boy to be on your
[Laughter]
staff that's from the book of buy Romy
that is well done wow I guess the crowd
was a little touchy about that one
I guess butt stuff's realing
tasteful next one an amazing journey
inside my mouth just me and my
dentist Alex bin uh chapter five because
your wife won't go on that Journey
[Applause]
anymore all right next one how to be a
doll detective Elementary Clues to
solving the mysteries of
dolls living doll Sam LaVine what's your
answer how to leave a note for when
you're eaten by your cats
yes they will eat you they will yeah
Greg proves this is from the forward
this is going to make you so
[Laughter]
[Applause]
sad now that the mystery solved I don't
know what to do with my life or my
nights I'd like to take an amazing
journey I'm sorry where inside your
mouth
oh
sold uh moving on the pole position is
stripping for
you and how to stay healthy doing it
Greg chapter seven when to put down the
little carpet all right
Alex bin chapter six getting out of John
mayor's
[Laughter]
trunk It also says look inside above the
book that's extra it
is yeah